uwcu.org 2017-04-16

# Your Privacy Is Important to Us - UW Credit Union (UWCU, University of Wisconsin Credit Union)

About UW Credit Union » Your Privacy Is Important to Us

Thank you for choosing UW Credit Union to assist you with your financial needs. It is our mission to provide you with excellent solutions and service, as well as to protect your personal financial information.

We are committed to maintaining the highest level of integrity in the protection and use of private member information. In fact, we follow strict business practices that exceed what is legally required.

> **Selling member information** —we never do it.
> 
> **Outside partnerships** —any outside vendor we do business with is required to keep your information private. Any joint marketing partner must keep your information confidential.

This notice details our practices in the collection and use of private information.

We appreciate your confidence and the opportunity to serve you. | _Rev. 7/11_  
---|---  
  
### Facts

| What does UW Credit Union do with your personal information?  
---|---  
**Why?** |  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
**What?** |  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

> Social Security number and account balances
> 
> Account transactions and credit card or other debt
> 
> Payment history and transaction history  
  
**How?** |  All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons UW Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
### Reasons we can share your personal information

| 

### Does UW Credit Union share?

| 

### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes –** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations or to report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes –** to offer our products and services to you | Yes | Yes  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –** information about your transactions and experiences | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –** information about your creditworthiness | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**For our nonaffiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
  
### To limit our sharing

| 

> Send us a Secure Message through Web Branch
> 
> Call us at 800.533.6773

**Please Note:** If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
  
### Questions?

| Call 800.533.6773 or go to uwcu.org  
---|---  
  
### Who We Are  
  
---  
**Who is providing this notice?** | UW Credit Union  
  
### What We Do  
  
---  
**How does UW Credit Union protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
**How does UW Credit Union collect my personal information?** | 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * Open an account or apply for a loan
  * Give us your employment information or show your driver's license
  * Use your credit or debit card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?** |  Your choices will apply to everyone on the account—unless you tell us otherwise.   
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** | 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.   
  
### Definitions  
  
---  
**Affiliates** | 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * CU Campus Resources

Nonaffiliates ****| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Government agencies (OFAC)
  * Plastic card processors (credit, debit, or ATM)
  * Financial statement publishers or printers
  * Mortgage service companies
  * Consumer reporting agencies
  * Data processors
  * Check/share draft printers

**Joint Marketing** | 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * UW Credit Union does not engage in joint marketing
